[
  {
    "id": "306",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is AWS Import/Export Disk?",
      "answers": [
        "A way of transferring your data into and out of AWS cloud using your own disk that you send to Amazon; the predecessor to Snowball",
        "A way of using Snowball to transfer data to AWS",
        "A type of Snowball Edge",
        "A type of Snowmobile"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["A way of transferring your data into and out of AWS cloud using your own disk that you send to Amazon; the predecessor to Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "307",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "What are the three different types of Snowball?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball", "Snowball Edge", "Snowmobile"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "308",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Snowball is a petabyte-scale data transport solution that uses a secure appliance to transfer large amounts of data into and out of AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "309",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Snowball has an 80TB size and 256-bit encryption?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "310",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Snowball is a 100TB data transfer device with on-board storage and compute capabilities?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowball Edge"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "311",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these are true about Snowball Edge?",
      "answers": [
        "Can be used as a temporary storage tier for large local datasets",
        "Can be used to support local workloads in remote or off-line locations",
        "Can be clustered together with other Snowball Edge devices to form a local storage tier and process your data on premises, letting your applications run even when that can't access the cloud",
        "Is a little AWS data center you can run on-premises which can run lambda functions",
        "Comes on a semi-trailer and in a shipping container"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Can be used as a temporary storage tier for large local datasets", "Can be used to support local workloads in remote or off-line locations", "Can be clustered together with other Snowball Edge devices to form a local storage tier and process your data on premises, letting your applications run even when that can't access the cloud", "Is a little AWS data center you can run on-premises which can run lambda functions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "312",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Snowball is for peta-byte or even exa-byte levels of data?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowmobile"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "313",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Snowball arrives in a shipping container and is hauled by a semi?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowmobile"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "314",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which Snowball can transfer 100PB per?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowmobile"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "315",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which Snowball can be used to transfer a complete data center migration to AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "Snowball",
        "Snowball Edge",
        "Snowmobile",
        "Import/Export Disk",
        "Snowman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Snowmobile"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "316",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Snowball has a client that you use to interface with it?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "317",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Snowball comes with a kindle that you use to interface with it?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "318",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the Snowball credentials?",
      "answers": [
        "unlock code",
        "Secret Key",
        "Access Key",
        "manifest file"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unlock code", "manifest file"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "319",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What does transfer acceleration use to speed up transfers to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudFront Edge Network",
        "Dedicated Connection",
        "Direct Connect",
        "Fiber Optic Lines"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudFront Edge Network"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "320",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 Transfer Acceleration uses a _______ to upload directly to an Edge Location which will then transfer that file to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudFront Edge Network",
        "Dedicated Connection",
        "Direct Connect",
        "distinct URL"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["distinct URL"]
    }
  }
]
